Bench, you want to
make an enemy of the
Sovereign Sanctum?
You blind fools think you’re worthy
of clinging to the Sovereign Sanctum?
Sandero.
You can doubt
it all you want.
When Steward Jeyn arrives,
you’ll
find out exactly.
ow you the hell is that?
Steward Jeyn is the
Sovereign Sanctum’s representative
in Emeraldstone.
Oh, just the
local steward of Emeraldstone.
No wonder I’ve
never heard of him.
What?
Are you saying Steward Jeyn isn’t
important
enough for you to know?
Exactly.
He clearly never received my orders
to the higher stewards:
do not abuse power,
do not bully the weak.
This Jeyn has
obviously ignored my rules.
Enough, Severin.
Drop the pathetic act.
I don’t care how you
leeched onto the Morellan family,
but insulting Steward Jeyn?
Don’t blame me when
I make you regret it.
You’ll make me regret it?
What gives you the right?
Do you truly
not understand who gave
you everything you have in Emeraldstone?
You’re saying you
gave it to me?
When I raised the
Scott family to the top,
you were still
digging in the mines.
Exactly.
You just latched
onto the Morellan family.
It’s not a big deal.
You’re wrong.
Marrying Lord Severin is
an honor for me.
I am the one who
is reaching above my station.
Insult him again and
I will have you killed.
I can’t stand
listening to him claim
he’s responsible for
the Scott family’s success.
If you don’t believe me,
use your communication stone right now
and ask Lord Campbell of the
Wastelands why he helped the
dying Scott family three years ago.
I can't stand listening to him claim he's
responsible for the Scott family's success.
If you don't believe me use your communication stone
right now and ask Lord Campbell of the wasteland why he
helped the dying Scott family three years ago.
How do you know about that?
Because I told him to.
Fine, I’ll call him.
Today I'm exposing your
lies in front of everyone!
Turn the volume up to maximum.
Let everyone hear.
Lady Livia, what can
I do for you?
Lord Campbell, sorry to bother you.
Just speak.
I wanted to ask
three years
ago, when you helped
my family,
was that your own decision?
Why are you asking
this now, Lady Livia?
Because some madman today
claimed he was the
one who told
you to help us.
I want to expose his
lie in front of everyone.
Who is this person?
It's my former fiancé,
the disowned
son of House Carter,
Severin Carter.